my-india.net 2013-05-03

# My-India.net: Privacy Policy

## The below privacy policy applies to all the MINET sites. 

This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to information practices related to our websites listed here. Although this website contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other sites. If you follow a link to another website you should carefully read their privacy policy. 

## Email address or any other Personal Information Collected on this Website

No personally-identifiable information (PII) is collected on this website from consumers that browse the website for information. The email address collected on this website is gathered on our "contact us" pages or through other email subscription services, where your email address is requested to send you the relevant information. We collect this information so that we can respond to the comments that you send to us or to send you the news or movie updates specifically requested by you through the respective pages. We will not rent, sell or share any PII about you with third parties for any reason except when required to assist in resolving an issue you raise with us or as required by law.

## Anonymous Information Collected on this Website

We record anonymous data such as traffic logs, number of visits or clicks on a given page, pages viewed or links to our site. We use IP addresses and cookies for gathering website statistics. We also store IP addresses on our server in the event that our site should become corrupted and it becomes necessary to discover the cause of this corruption. 

We aggregate this anonymous data as part of managing, maintaining and reporting on use of our website. We may share this anonymous data with third parties for the limited purpose of reporting on use of our website, or to comply with applicable law. We do not rent, sell or share any anonymous data collected on this website with third parties for marketing purposes. 

None of this anonymous data is linked to personally-identifiable information and we make no attempt to link IP addresses to the individuals who visit this site. 

## Third Party Advertisements

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

## Cookies

We use cookies on this website. Cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of your online patterns and preferences, as well as identify you as a return visitor. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information from scratch upon each visit to a given website. We serve a cookie from our website when members log in to member-only pages, so that they can navigate those pages on the site. A randomly-generated anonymous identifier is assigned to that cookie to enable this process. We also serve a cookie to note the anonymous web traffic described in the previous section of this Privacy Policy. No personally-identifiable information is collected by or linked to any of the cookies delivered on our site. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the MINET sites. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to MINET web users based on their visit to MINET sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy located at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.  You have the ability to manage the use of cookies on your computer using controls in your web-browser. To learn more about how to manage cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. 

## Web Beacons

Some of our advertisers may use web beacons. Generally, a Web beacon consists of a small string of software code that represents a graphic image request on a Web page or email. There may or may not be a visible graphic image associated with the Web beacon and often the image is designed to blend into the background of a Web page or email. Web beacons can be used for many purposes - including site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, and personalization. A significant majority of Web beacons collect only anonymous data. However, some may be used to collect PII, particularly in the case of email that contains a Web beacon. In such cases, the data collected through the Web beacon may be linked to the recipient's email address or other information identifying the recipient.

## Google Ads

We use third-party advertising company, Google, to regularly serve ads when you visit our website. Google or it's advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit here: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As  we evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to reflect those changes, where applicable. We therefore reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect. 

## Questions?

Please contact us with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.
